#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/duc-n-ba1360142 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Elicitation
Business Process Model
Business Data Model

# Duc N.

Senior IT Business Analyst Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

### Summary

IT Business Analyst with 7+ of experience of discovering business growth opportunities with IT solutions with variety industries (Financial Services, Real Estate, e-Commerce). Well-versed in analyzing issue and developing actionable insights that support decision-making. Gain buy-in to workflow improvements by putting complex ideas in clear terms for both technical and non-technical colleagues. Adapting readily to new work challenges and industry conditions.

## Experience

Freelance Information Technology Business Analyst July 2023 - Present (1 year 9 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

#### **FE CREDIT**

Senior Information Technology Business Analyst December 2023 - Present (1 year 4 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Mirae Asset Finance Company (Vietnam) Senior Product Lead Executive July 2022 - June 2023 (1 year) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Hung Thinh Corporation Information Technology Business Analyst May 2020 - July 2022 (2 years 3 months)

Freelance
Product Owner
October 2019 - April 2020 (7 months)

Easy Credit Vietnam
Information Technology Business Analyst
October 2018 - September 2019 (1 year)

Sendo.vn Information Technology Business Analyst January 2017 - May 2018 (1 year 5 months)

### Education

Ho Chi Minh University Food and Industry
Bachelor's Software Engineer, Computer Software Technology/
Technician · (2012 - 2016)

National Institute of Information Technology
Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering · (2010 - 2013)